getepic.com 2015-09-19

# Epic! - Books for Kids

Welcome to Epic!. We're glad you want to use the leading streaming service for children's books and other content. We value the privacy of all of our users and we know you care about your privacy and the privacy of your children, so we created this Privacy Policy. It explains the information we collect from users and how and when we disclose or use it. By accessing or using the Epic! website, services, software, applications, and/or content made available by Epic! Creations, Inc., "Epic!" (" **the Epic! Service", "we",** and **"us"** ), you are consenting to collection and use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. When you use the Epic! Service, you also agree to our **Terms of Service** [www.getepic.com/tos](http://www.getepic.com/tos)

Data Collection of Personally Identifiable Information When you sign up for the Epic! app on your iOS or Android device, YOU, as a parent, may be asked to provide your email address. This type of information is considered personally identifiable information. Epic! uses this type of information in the following ways: 1) To send you feedback on your child's reading progress 2) To communicate with you about purchases 3) To send you updates about the Epic! Service and/or 4) For gathering anonymous aggregate information from all our users Our service providers or partners may have access to your personally identifiable information as necessary to provide their services. They are required to maintain the privacy of all such information in their possession or control and can only use the information for the purpose that we have contracted them. We use commercially reasonable efforts to require them to safeguard your personal information and limit their use of it. We do not sell email addresses to third parties for any purpose. We, at Epic!, as well as any agents and affiliates with whom we may work, maintain the privacy of all information collected.  

## Children's Privacy

Although we collect personally identifiable information from parents, we do not collect such information from your child. Any child under the age of 13 using the service must do so with permission from a parent. All full names, email addresses, and credit card billing information must be from a parent or guardian. We do not knowingly collect personal information (including full name, email address, telephone number or home address) from children under the age of 13 in our app. We encourage parents to take an active role in their children's activities and interests on their devices. When registering your child with the service, Epic! may ask a series of general questions including your child's age, interests and gender. This information is used to customize content to your child's age and interests. We do not use or disclose this information for any other purposes except to provide you with quality service. Any data that is shared is done so on an anonymous, aggregate basis among all users or is related to communicating reading behavior patterns to publishers.

## Data Usage / Cookies / Data Automatically Collected

As many apps do, Epic! collects information on the way you use our application. This information is routinely gathered to help us understand and track usage and behavior, analyze trends, and to continuously improve the user experience for you and your child. Third Party Applications and Websites Although the Epic! app is a safe place for kids, a child may leave the Epic! app using the iOS or Android device Home button. Should your child leave the Epic! app for another application or browser, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. We have no control over how other applications or sites collect, distribute or otherwise use your personal information or how they safeguard and secure your personal information.

## Security

In circumstances where your personal information is collected, we may use procedural and digital security measures that are designed to help protect against loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of information and data, such as password protection and secure socket layer.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change or modify our Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a revised Privacy Policy on our site. As an ongoing user of the Epic! app, you will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy. We ask that you refer to the Privacy Policy on a continuing basis so that you understand our current privacy practices.

## Unsubscribing, Questions, Feedback

If you would like to opt out of communication from Epic! you can do so by emailing: unsubscribe@getepic.com. If you would like to contact us with questions or feedback, please email: support@getepic.com. 

Epic! is owned and operated by Epic! Creations, Inc., 702 Marshall Street, Suite 280, Redwood City, CA 94063.

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is November, 15, 2013.
